question_data = [
        {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "AMC&#039;s &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;, Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were introduced to us in Season 1.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                           "question": "A group of islands is called an &#039;archipelago&#039;.",
                                           "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The &quot;Gympie Stinger&quot; is the deadliest plant in the world.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                          "question": "Kangaroos keep food in their pouches next to their children.",
                                          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language &quot;Simlish&quot; was The Sims (2000).",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "A defibrillator is used to start up a heartbeat once a heart has stopped beating.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Shrimp can swim backwards.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
         "question": "It was once believed that injecting shark cartilage into people would prevent them from contracting cancer.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The game &quot;Battlefield 1&quot; takes place during World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In Kingdom Hearts the Paopu fruit is said to intertwine the destinies for two people forever.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                           "question": "A bear does NOT defecate during hibernation. ",
                                           "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                          "question": "Vietnam is the only country in the world that starts with V. ",
                                          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                          "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Zeus can control lightning.",
                                          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Ottawa is the capital of Canada.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Russia passed a law in 2013 which outlaws telling children that homosexuals exist.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Adolf Hitler was a german soldier in World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
         "question": "In Undertale, having a &quot;Fun Value&quot; set to 56-57 will play the &quot;Wrong Number Song Call&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "There are no deserts in Europe.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In the &quot;Half-Life&quot; series, &quot;H.E.V&quot; stands for &quot;Hazardous Evasiveness Vest&quot;",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In the TV series Red Dwarf, Kryten&#039;s full name is Kryten 2X4B-523P.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
         "question": "DHCP stands for Dynamic Host Configuration Port.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                          "question": "United States President Ronald Reagan was the first president to appoint a woman to the Supreme Court. ",
                                          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "A flock of crows is known as a homicide.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Cave Crawler&quot; will attack you.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                          "question": "The Hundred Years&#039; War was fought for more than a hundred years.",
                                          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Oxford University is older than the Aztec Empire. ", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Klingons respect their disabled comrades, and those who are old, injuried, and helpless.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
         "question": "The board game Go has more possible legal positions than the number of atoms in the visible universe.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
         "question": "In Topology, the complement of an open set is a closed set.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                           "question": "Hungary is the only country in the world beginning with H.",
                                           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In &quot;League of Legends&quot;, there exists four different types of Dragon.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In the Season One Championship of &quot;League of Legends&quot;, the highest achievable rank was Diamond.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
         "question": "The song Scatman&#039;s World was released after Scatman (Ski-Ba-Bop-Ba-Dop-Bop).",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Nova Scotia is on the east coast of Canada.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The scrapped Sonic the Hedgehog 2 level &quot;Hidden Palace Zone&quot; was later reused in the iOS port of the game. ",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "A Facebook campaign placed Rage Against The Machine&#039;s &quot;Killing in the Name Of&quot; as the UK Christmas Number 1 in 2009.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Venus of Willendorf is one of the earliest works of art, depicting the planets Mars and Venus embrace in the heavens at night.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "ATP tennis hosted several tournaments on carpet court before being replaced to reduce injuries.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
         "question": "Only one country in the world starts with the letter Q.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
